♪ ~
Congratulations to Yamazoe and the two on their marriage.
It's like the three of us got married.
toast
I'm glad you're letting me talk to you.
Oh, it's delicious.
Can I have a bite?
Really?
Easy to drink.
that's just what you (he) deserves
They're husband and wife.
We drank the same glass and now I'm a little nervous.
We were the first couple to perform together.
Because it's nice to have the two of you on TV in the first place.
Honestly, there are shows you want to be in and there are shows you never want to be in.
Couple.
I see
I see... that's what you're saying.
Is there a show you don't want to be in, just the two of you?
If Mr. Nagano was there, you would definitely not like it, he said.
(after the stem of an adjective) seeming ...
I absolutely hate it.
be hard to do
I'll be back with Marco Polo food and other things in shreds.
Don't say it.
Cut up.
I like the people on the show a lot, but they're too scary.
There's not a millimeter of real waka in that show.
No, now, that guy and its m2
lime
Lime.
Thank you for watching!
What do you call each other?
I get asked this for sure.
I'm sure they'll ask.
I call him Rin-kun, usually.
Your first name.
I usually call him by his first name.
Mr. Dekami, I don't know your real name.
My real name is Yuki.
Yuki?
We call it hem hem hem.
Hem hem hem?
Ninja spirit?
That hem hem hem.
It's too embarrassing.
Because they look alike?
Really no hassle whatsoever.
The first time I said, "Hem Hem Hem, you know..." it was like...
Hemu.
I responded.
I thought it was hem-hem.
You're making your own decisions.
I was reacting to it.
I responded, and the last thing I did was get called away.
I've called an infinite number of them.
You know, like, "Hey, fishy.
Potato Boy said...
I've been called a lot of things.
When I said, "Hem hem hem is...
Because I said hemu.
Finally, I knew it was hemming and hawing.
I don't remember that at all.
I'm forced to admit it.
I say this in various mediums, but if you ask me a question.
What type of woman do you like?
I like funny people.
Satsuma River itself
It's so cozy.
It's very nice.
We're at the same point where we think it's interesting.
It's the same.
That's the best I can do.
Can I say something?
Can a stranger come in?
Can I tell you a funny story?
It's neither Satsumagawa nor Rin.
We slept together... in the morning.
I'd still like to sleep a little longer.
I was in a daze.
Then Dekami woke up first.
I'll start with this part of me.
He came at me with a tsun.
And I'm the one with the...
I said, "Ah.
I'll see you next time I'm here.
He came at me with a tsun.
And I'm the one with the...
I said woo.
Sound changed.
If you touch me here, I'll, uh...
If you touch me here, I'm going to say, "Woo.
So some kind of rule has been established.
He started doing something amazing.
And I'm suddenly in the middle of it.
I don't care where they touch me anymore.
not responding
It went like this.
then
I've done something I can't take back.
Seriously, isn't it interesting?
Nice comment.
That's really interesting, isn't it?
I'm too embarrassed.
shy
He won't get off... from the contraption.
that's so, isn't it
I'd like that.
That's great. That's great. I'm so jealous.
I still really want to say this to everyone.
I want to brag about how interesting it is.
This is so good!
shy
I don't know... you're a fan.
The world didn't find out?
even if you go out with him
Surprisingly, I didn't hide it very well.
He usually said something like "rice.
Did anyone talk to you?
I used to get approached a lot.
When only this one was approached.
I'm really good at mimicking a woman who is nothing to me.
Can you mimic?
I can do it.
It's hard.
In general.
I think I may not have known about it in the first place.
Once that rainbow twilight
When I was approached by Kamaboko Gymnasium
I thought I'd been found by someone who would talk about it like this.
Hey, just now, when I was like, hey, I'm with a woman.
What's your seniority? Something like that.
Let's get you out of here.
Have you ever worked with him?
I'm also co-starring with Mr. Kamaboko.
Unnoticed?
I knew it wasn't the opposite sex.
You didn't find out?
They didn't find out at all.
Make it sound like you're some kind of interesting senior.
It's really insanely good.
Can you get through it?
Yes, sir.
I'll do it too.
You're doing a good job.
not at all (with neg. verb)
I'm still a human being.
I'm a ninja dog.
It's too realistic.
It's not real hem hem hem.
Hem is just someone who responded once.
I'm good at sinabras.
Does Mr. Yamazoe have anyone swamping him right now?
The one you're swamping?
What do you mean?
Is there someone you think is pretty good looking?
You mean like that sex thing?
We've all been muddling through.
All together.
sex friend (someone with whom one is not romantically involved but frequently has sexual relations with anyway)
Yes, yes, yes!
common dolphin (Delphinus delphis)
I'll see you then.
I can say it... you can say it.
Because they probably think so, too.
He's playing with me.
I don't know what kind of person is your type.
Are you sure that's the type you like?
You know, my favorite type.
I wrote it down the other day.
What?
You get asked that a lot.
But being nice?
I always felt like I was in a weird mood.
So you said that's what I think is the point of someone I like.
in one's heart
People with normal senses.
You know, like finances.
straightforward (plain) common-sense man
I'd like to have some common sense.
A real one.
I've been told it's a snack bar.
You're going to betray me like that?
It's okay today.
It's a real, real, real thing.
Let's get serious, people.
You mean like Mr. Izumi Bingo?
not at all (with neg. verb)
close (e.g. of a theatrical performance)
I'm going to get flamed if I don't tweak it.
close (i.e. a close call)
When I got involved in saying no.
In a snack bar like this.
You're gonna be popular, no matter what you do.
No, no, no, no, no.
not at all (with neg. verb)
You'll definitely be popular with the ladies.
Because it's just not right to be in debt.
Ah, debt already.
one's step (as in "watch your step")
You also gamble, don't you?
I love you already.
Marriage and all that.
I don't want to get into debt.
I don't like it.
Gambling?
They don't even gamble.
What? That's so good.
No drinking, gambling, or smoking.
That's right, you can drink too.
What? That's great.
What's not to like? From my wife's point of view.
Like, you want me to fix this one thing.
What? You want me to fix it.
What is it?
I wonder.
Oh, it's something really like, for example.
You say, "If you put a cup here, it's dangerous, so don't do it.
And they'll say, "Okay, I've learned.
That's a good answer.
(esp. of men) one's prime (approx. age 30)
It's supposed to be here.
Doesn't this mean it's dangerous because it will fall?
But I can only input the information that I'm not supposed to put it here, so I put it here or something.
Uh-oh.
He said that there are a lot of things like that.
But I already know that.
cute
I say
Eh, you really love it, don't you?
stockpile
Now that you mention it, I see that I have that in me.
I don't know, I just want to do it again.
I see
good relationship
I don't know, I can't recognize it myself, so I'm not really sure.
So there was that solitary pin-up kind of side.
It's also true that there is an inner Satsakawarin.
The inner Sasakawa Rin is also a little bit out of place with other people.
I know.
I thought he was surprisingly true to his artistic style.
(Edo period) streetwalker
I think.
Is there a reverse, or do you want me to fix it?
When I lived alone, I was pretty much that
yeah
Like turning a house into a garbage dump.
I'm going to be in a place that's so trashed that they'll be filming a trash house.
That's right.
I'm pretty much incapable of cleaning up or anything.
But I totally like it.
what the hell is this?
Thank you.
I totally like that part too.
I got tired of telling them until I wanted them to fix it.
I didn't have to fix it.
I really did, but at some point I thought, "Why don't I just clean it up?
thankful
very
That made me more aware of life.
very good
What's the best way to do it?
He's funny and kind.
That's perfect.
Maybe they'll wake me up if I tell them.
They wake me up.
I knew I wanted a partner like this.
that's so, isn't it
You're probably right.
No, thank you, but it's the secret to the secret.
I'd pretty much like to say that it's frustrating and damaging.
Certainly each other.
Well, that's about as good as it gets.
I'm just saying, "Are you ready?
No, this is the two of them.
Will there be more work for the two of us to work together?
Will it increase?
I'm not sure if it's funny when he talks, but I'm not sure.
Feels good, doesn't it?
I think a lot of people want to hear more.
It's just normal and realistic.
I often get people saying, "This music is good.
I'm pretty sure I'd get into it with you.
I love Halo Pro so much.
Halopro trainees
I'm going to be in Halo Pro from now on.
As you become a member.
of those who become members.
There was a weekly program that followed the trainees closely.
It's called Halodori.
That's also what he said at first, "Let's watch this together.
A program about the struggles of middle school students who don't know each other.
If you look at it while saying "eh"...
I'm really into it and I'm...
Morning Musume's current active members. who is currently a member of
I don't have a good grasp of the names of the members.
The newest tea group called Umama.
I made my debut in Halo Pro.
You can recognize all the members of Ocha-no-Uma, can't you?
Eh, I'm hooked.
I'm totally hooked.
Under the influence of Mr. Dejin
That's right.
Momo Kitahara of Ocha-no-Uma blogged
R1 Grand Prix Kaz Sasaoka was the funniest!
He's my guess for the comedian.
You write.
You didn't write it down.
Momochan probably likes comedy too.
If you announce your marriage, you can blog about it that day.
He said congratulations to Kaz Sasaoka and Dejin.
I was so happy.
You write.
Two people who love each other.
I saw it and decided to check out Momochan's blog.
I was so happy.
I'm so excited.
Dejin-san by Kazu Sasaoka, a favorite of mine.
Did you get something like this?
They tell me about comedians I don't know, and so on.
But yes, there is one thing I would like you to fix.
I just remembered something in this vein.
Well, there are times when we fight.
I pretty much only talk to about two people I would call my best friends.
This kind of thing could lower the reputation of comedian Kazu Sasaoka RPG.
I try not to tell too many people about it.
I'm so worried.
But in the middle of a fight backstage at the theater or something.
Or consulting with Mr. Kitsujineiri.
Different office.
I'm very close with Mr. Kanazawa TKC Factory, and we consult with seniors.
I can still understand if you want to talk to the guys you usually listen to at home.
It's a comedian I've never heard of called "The Next Year's Girl.
That's the only thing I really don't say.
Sometimes, when we fought, I'd go stay at a junior's house.
That's totally fine.
When we made up, whose house did they let me stay in this time?
I told him that he had to say thank you for letting me stay here.
Who's that in the second girl's house? I said, "Who?
Talk to a stranger
I was wondering if you could narrow the scope of the consultation a bit more.
That's because you've got the wrong information.
I talked to the next year's daughter about it, but I didn't stay at her house.
It was Yotaro who stayed at the house.
Yotaro's Jackson One
Yotaro's Jackson
Thank you, but who?
That's all I'm serious about.
It's a little bit like a new character coming out at the right time for a consultation.
I'd like you to talk about it on a regular basis.
Do you ever fight with people you like, Mom?
You know, like a struggle.
I've been in fights, of course.
Doer at home? Do you do it at home? No?
At home
The doer.
I'm a doer.
I think I'm going to get it.
I tend to say too much.
I thought if I said more, I'd hurt you.
Because you're not going to think it, you're going to say words you'll regret later.
I'm going to run and get the hell out of here.
Because if I were there, I would have already said it.
I don't know where to go to someone's house.
I want you to introduce me to Yotaro.
Yotaro, at your house.
What did you say in your post?
Aren't there many short people like Yotaro?
I don't write in people's houses very often.
Are you the kind of person who is suited for love?
I don't know.
I can't imagine.
What kind of people do you like?
from the start
I'm curious.
This is why I'm pretty particular.
that's right
Kind and funny.
I don't get out of the house much.
indoor
You woke me up in the morning.
I am.
even if you lose your temper
It.
Someone to wrap up with.
in Tokyo
after-effect
People who are not gourmets.
Who isn't gourmandizing?
No gourmetization.
It's going to be very hard.
(sentence end) indicates emphasis, agreement, request for confirmation, etc.
and no one comes up to me.
Or rather, they don't come close to me even if they don't.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
An example of a mom
abrupt
therefore
My only
just a minute
He's been a good friend to me for a long time.
Yabati Naribobo-chan.
Married to Acorn Takeshi.
Did you introduce that too?
But it's more like an introduction.
Or maybe it's because of the Satsuma River.
Usually with Acorn, too.
Stay close.
If you like Yavati, tell him we should go see him live.
We were friends, so we went to the Yavati concert.
Then let's all go out to dinner sometime.
that's all I'm saying.
From then on, I really noticed.
There's a romance in the air.
I'm sure there's someone out there you'd like to recommend.
isn't it?
I was going to ask you to introduce me.
I'm Cupid?
But there is Jesus Akito.
Certainly yes Akito.
He's over here.
Very nearby and bizarre.
Why is it bizarre, bizarre bound?
It doesn't have to be tied to the bizarre.
Yes Akito.
What else do you need to know about the bizarre? Dekami...
But that can't be true.
I don't think so.
It's pretty normal for a comedian to be like this.
I have a couple of good friends.
Like Team Kondo-san.
Hey, Kon-chan.
I knew it.
And Team Kondo is much kinder.
gentle
I want someone nice.
You don't look like a gourmet at all.
I'm not a gourmet.
Ah, but surprisingly
Team Kondo-san, gourmet!
Wow!
cheap everyday food that most people enjoy (e.g. ramen, curry, etc.)
And you usually shouldn't go out with them at all.
normally
It's not balanced.
Not like a condition or something?
Yes, sir.
What are the words of the proposal?
I'll ask.
No, this is the only way to propose.
What? What?
What what what?
Let's get married!
Gags in motion.
The words of the proposal itself are
It's so normal.
He asked me to marry him.
I was told in Enoshima.
It's our first date.
Go with me to the former location.
Don't say it, don't say it.
even
Lynn in gag language is embarrassing.
Lynn created the
I got the amazing feeling that it was Satsuma River.
From proposal to enrollment
I had a little time.
Back then...
Just in time.
R-1's artistic career restrictions.
Whether or not the repeal has been declared.
Has it been announced yet?
Last year R-1 is over.
I thought.
Even last year I thought the last year was over.
With the R-1 finished.
Something's going on with the R-1 loss.
And I've been looking at it.
When adjusting for award races.
I think I'd do a comedian.
I think they do a lot of recording and stuff like that.
Like measuring fractions.
The R-1 is gone.
well, you know...
You're thinking of me.
I was feeling that.
To be honest, even in everyday life and stuff.
The proposal itself
He asked me to marry him.
It was just an ordinary word.
You were recording?
You were measuring?
I was being measured.
Isn't it very scary?
until he agreed to propose to me.
I was measuring.
I was forced to go dark.
forced blackout
He thought I was an award winner.
I don't think prize races.
Too bad, huh?
You don't think "yes" means no.
I was really surprised.
We're about to close.
Oh, no, it didn't take long.
Something I left out or something.
I've heard so many valuable things.
I could really hear it.
seriously
Really.
I was right
what
It's the best one.
the highest
I'm good at gags and stuff.
I'll take that one too, please.
Do you have any happy gags?
Happy Gag
Yes, sir.
Waitress, get her a Romanée Conti. I'll get the chorizo.
Last-minute gifts
happiness
happy gag
It's good chorizo, but...
Then please leave now.
You don't talk like that.
That was a delicious meal (said after meals)
We had a great time.
Thank you.
I wish you all the best, Mr. Yamazoe.
I got a good one. It's going to be a good one.
sephret
Safret, let's get serious.
You'll get serious when you see it.
This is how they're born.
Aren't you alone?
the worst
Worst.
Thank you for watching!